I see you have a heart for God.
You love Jesus. You're always in the church.
Yes.
Praising God but there is an evil spirit in your life.
Yes!
A demon possesses you.
That is why I've come here.
Before now, you keep asking yourself, "What kind of spirit is this?"
But this time, he appeared to you face to face, physically.
You can see physically that a demon is using your body as a dwelling place.
In fact, it chased me from the US to here.
It kept attacking me in the dream, even when I'm not sleeping,
like wrestling with me.
And I came here to...
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
It's out.
In Jesus Christ's name.
It has destroyed you, destroyed your family, destroyed everything, your career.
You're an elder in the church.
Yes.
Can you see demon? Demon is a foolish thing
and it's now tormenting an elder in the church.
But it's over now. It will never come on you again.
Seriously, I was thinking, when I get back to the US,
I'm not going back to that church again.
The church I was going to was a redeemed church.
I don't know where this demon came from.
As an elder, don't leave the church. Stay in the church.
- The demon will not torment you again.
- Amen.
Continue your services of God there, don't leave the place.
I'll be your friend, your partner in prayer.
Amen! Thank You, Jesus! Thank You, Lord!
Prophecy Confirmation
Sir, we welcome you to The Synagogue Church once again, in Jesus' name.
Can you please tell us your name and where you come from.
My name is Moses Adeola.
I'm from Osun State, Nigeria but I came from the US because I'm based in the US.
Tell us the message of prophecy you've received from the anointed man of God.
During the worship, the man of God called me out and said
that I have a heart for God,
I've never missed church,
that I'm always in the church praising God - in fact, that is true -
and that I'm an elder in the church but I have this demonic attack all the time.
This is true, I confirm it.
As a matter of fact, before I left the US, that was part of the problem.
The demonic attack comes all the time, it lives inside me.
I see you have a heart for God. You love Jesus.
You are always in the church.
Yes.
Praising God but there is an evil spirit in your life.
A demon possesses you.
That is why I have come here.
Before now, you keep asking yourself, "What kind of spirit is this?"
But this time, he appeared to you face to face, physically.
You can see physically that a demon is using your body as a dwelling place.
In fact, before I left, I had to struggle with it,
like we were struggling with one another.
I had to beat him out and run out.
It was like the demon was chasing me,
even to come to Nigeria, because when I was in the plane, I still saw it
and when I arrived in Nigeria, I still saw it.
So, I was confused about that.
Sir, you mean, all what the man of God said about you is true.
That is, you have a heart for God, and you love God,
you're always in the church praising God but there's a demon that lives inside you,
that uses your body and it even manifests to you in the physical.
Can you tell us, how did the man of God put the prophecy?
Yes, what the man of God said was true.
I love God.
I like to worship.
He said that this demonic attack had possessed me,
a demon lives inside me, my body.
It is true because I see it even when I'm not sleeping.
So, what the man of God said was true.
Okay, do you believe now that this prophecy you have received today
has put an end to this common calamity of human life that you've been experiencing?
Yes, I believe. The man of God prayed for me and the Lord revealed it to him.
I believe that I have overcome it.
I have the victory now and I thank God for it.
Amen. And the man of God also told you in the prophecy
that you should not leave the church
since you have decided to remain in God's presence to praise Him -
you should not allow this problem to make you to leave the presence of God.
Is that true for your life?
Yes, that is true because the demonic attack was so much.
I didn't know where it was coming from
so I said, when I get back to the US, I'm going to quit going to that church
and then go to the Lord and pray, to see where the Lord will lead me.
But the man of God advised me to stay there and not to quit the church.
You are an elder in the church.
Yes.
Can you see demon? A demon is a foolish thing
and it's now tormenting an elder in the church.
But it's over now. It will never come on you again.
Seriously, I was thinking, when I get back to the US,
I'm not going back to that church again.
The church I was going to was a redeemed church.
I don't know where this demon came from.
As an elder, don't leave the church, stay in the church.
- The demon will not torment you again.
- Amen.
Continue your services of God there, don't leave the place.
I'll be your friend, your partner in prayer.
I agreed with him.
To God be the glory. We thank God Almighty for this wonderful revelation and deliverance
that you have received today through the message of prophecy.
And we want to encourage you as a believer in Christ Jesus
to maintain your stand in Christ Jesus and make the Word of God the standard for your life.
Remember that sometimes foolish things may happen
to strengthen our desire and our determination to follow our Lord Jesus Christ.
As you make the Word of God the standard for your life today,
this wonderful deliverance you've received through the prophecy
will be permanent in your life, in Jesus' name.
Amen, I receive that.
Thank you very much.
Prophecy Continues
RV: Mel Flowers 28/04/2019